<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam Robbins&#39; Website on ChL&#39;s New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://summit1876.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sam Robbins&#39; Website on ChL&#39;s New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 15:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://summit1876.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Portfolio Website</title>
      <link>https://summit1876.github.io/portfolio/hugo-portfolio-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://summit1876.github.io/portfolio/hugo-portfolio-website/</guid>
      <description>I created my portfolio website using Hugo and UIKit, it serves as an online resume containing all my work.
This has been created as a theme so that others can use and adapt it.
Sections Homepage The homepage provides the basic information about you, including links to social media, skills you have, things you&amp;rsquo;ve done and your education. This page makes good use of UIKit grid and cards for organising all the information and ensuring it is responsive to work on mobile devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team project without GitHub</title>
      <link>https://summit1876.github.io/portfolio/example-team-no-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://summit1876.github.io/portfolio/example-team-no-github/</guid>
      <description>This is some content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a new Website</title>
      <link>https://summit1876.github.io/blog/first-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://summit1876.github.io/blog/first-blog/</guid>
      <description>For a long time this website has had a couple of links to contact me, but those days are over.
Now I have a brand new Hugo website with a custom written theme complete with
 A homepage with more social links, and description of my skills An about page with description of who I am A portfolio page to showcase all my projects A blog  Why Hugo? The first question is why a site builder?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Song</title>
      <link>https://summit1876.github.io/blog/second_blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://summit1876.github.io/blog/second_blog/</guid>
      <description>My favorite Album : Frank Ocean - Blonde
My favorite Song : Frank Ocean - Pink + White
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uzS3WG6__G4
Lyrics
Yeah, yeah oh
Yeah, yeah yeah
That&amp;rsquo;s the way everyday goes
Every time we&amp;rsquo;ve no control If the sky is pink and white If the ground is black and yellow It&amp;rsquo;s the same way you showed me Nod my head, don&amp;rsquo;t close my eyes Halfway on a slow move It&amp;rsquo;s the same way you showed me If you could fly then you&amp;rsquo;d feel south Up north&amp;rsquo;s getting cold soon The way it is, we&amp;rsquo;re on land So I&amp;rsquo;m someone to hold true Keep you cool when it&amp;rsquo;s still alive Won&amp;rsquo;t let you down when it&amp;rsquo;s all ruin Just the same way you showed me, showed me You showed me love Glory from above Regard my dear It&amp;rsquo;s all downhill from here In the wake of a hurricane Dark skin of a summer shade Nosedive in the flood lines Tall tower of milk crates It&amp;rsquo;s the same way you showed me Cannonball off the porch side Older kids trying off the roof Just the same way you showed me (You showed) If you could die and come back to life Up for air from the swimming pool You&amp;rsquo;d kneel down to the dry land Kiss the Earth that birthed you Gave you tools just to stay alive And make it out when the sun is ruined That&amp;rsquo;s the same way you showed me, showed me You showed me love Glory from above Regard my dear It&amp;rsquo;s all downhill from here Remember life Remember how it was Climb trees, Michael Jackson, it all ends here Say what up to Matthew, to Shoob Say what up to Danny Say what up to life immortality Bending up my Nikes Running out the melpomene, nicotine Stealing granny cigs (Take it easy) Gimme something sweet Bitch, I might like immortality This is life, life immortality</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
